Finding Aid to the Georgia O'Keeffe Photographs, 1882-1974, undated MS.37
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- Photographs, circa 1908-1964, undated; 1; 2938
  - Georgia O'Keeffe carrying clothing, circa 1912-1918; 2014.3.233; 3023; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.5 x 2.5 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with dog in Amarillo, Texas, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.234; 3022; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.5 x 2.5 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe in Texas, circa 1912-1918; 2014.3.235; 3021; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 2.25 x 3.25 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, 1942; 2014.3.236; 3020; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.5 x 2.5 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.237; 3019; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5.5 x 3.25 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1912-1914; 2014.3.238; 3018; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5 x 3 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with friends in boat, 1908; 2014.3.239; 3017; Unknown; 1 Cubic Feet Black and white photograph 3.125 x 3.875 inches (Box 3)
  - Unidentified woman, undated; 2014.3.240; 3016; Unknown; 1 Cubic Feet Black and white photograph 3.25 x 1.875 inches (Box 3)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe portrait as a child, undated; 2014.3.241; 3015; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.5 x 3.5 inches (Box 3)
  - Aunt Ollie, Aunt Lola, Georgia O'Keeffe, and Francis, Jr. in Front of Brick Building, undated; 2014.3.242; 3014; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Tintype 4.75 x 3.125 inches (Box 5)
  - Reproduction of Nude Series VIII by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.243; 3013; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 10 x 8 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of Nude Series XII by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.244; 3012; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8 x 10 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of From the Plains painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.245; 3011; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8 x 10 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of Rib and Jawbone painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.246; 3010; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8 x 10 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of Cliffs Beyond Abiquiu - Dry Waterfall painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.247; 3009; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 10 x 8 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of Spring painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.248; 3008; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8.875 x 7.75 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of Green Patio Door painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.249; 3007; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 10 x 8 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of The House I Live In painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.250; 3006; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8 x 10 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of Three Small Rocks Big painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.251; 3005; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8 x 10 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of Red Poppy painting by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.252; 3004; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 7.25 x 9.25 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of From the Lake No. III by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.253; 3003; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 10 x 8 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of White Place in Shadow by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.254; 3002; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 10.875 x 8.25 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of Shelton with Sun Spots by Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.255; 3001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 6 x 3.75 inches (Box 3)
  - Reproduction of a painting of Georgia O'Keeffe, undated; 2014.3.256; 3000; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 10 x 8.75 inches (Oversize 2)
  - Sculpture by Mary Callery in snow, undated; 2014.3.257; 2999; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 8 x 10 inches (Box 3)
  - Sculpture by Mary Callery in snow, undated; 2014.3.258; 2998; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 6.75 x 7 inches (Box 3)
  - Bamboo Spray, Chinese Ming by Wang Fu, undated; 2014.3.259; 2997; Fogg Art Museum; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 10 x 8 inches (Box 3)
    Copyright Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University
  - Sailboat on water, undated; 2014.3.260; 2996; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph, 13.375 x 10 in 13.375 x 10 inches (Oversize 2)
  - Canyon, undated; 2014.3.261; 2995; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 4.75 x 6.625 inches (Box 3)
  - Abiquiu house, salita door, undated; 2014.3.262; 2994; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 4.5 x 6.25 inches (Box 3)
  - Abiquiu house, zaguan door from exterior, undated; 2014.3.263; 2993; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 3.625 x 5.5 inches (Box 3)
  - Cliffs, New Mexico, undated; 2014.3.264; 2992; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4 x 5 inches (Box 3)
  - Ghost Ranch sign and skull, undated; 2014.3.265; 2991; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4 x 5 inches (Box 3)
  - Road and hill, New Mexico, undated; 2014.3.266; 2990; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4 x 5 inches (Box 3)
  - Skull hanging on brick chimney in city, undated; 2014.3.267; 2989; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5.75 x 3.75 inches (Box 3)
  - Ghost Ranch house exterior, undated; 2014.3.268; 2988; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 5 x 5 inches (Box 3)
  - Ghost Ranch patio and Pedernal, undated; 2014.3.269; 2987; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 5 x 5 inches (Box 3)
  - Abiquiu house exterior, west side garden with lilac bush, undated; 2014.3.270; 2986; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 5 x 5 inches (Box 3)
  - Skull, Ghost Ranch, undated; 2014.3.271; 2985; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Diffusion transfer print 4.375 x 7.5 inches (Box 4)
  - Skull, Ghost Ranch, undated; 2014.3.272; 2984; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Diffusion transfer print 4.375 x 7.5 inches (Box 4)
  - Abiquiu house, sitting room (contact sheet), before 1965; 2014.3.273; 2983; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Contact sheet 1.75 x 5.5 inche (Box 4)
  - Abiquiu house, sitting room, before 1965; 2014.3.274; 2982; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.25 x 5 inches (Box 4)
  - Abiquiu house, sitting room, before 1965; 2014.3.275; 2981; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.25 x 5 inches (Box 4)
  - Abiquiu house, bedroom window from exterior, undated; 2014.3.276; 2980; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.25 x 4.5 inches (Box 4)
  - Dead tree, New Mexico, undated; 2014.3.277; 2979; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 8 x 9.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Dead tree, New Mexico, undated; 2014.3.278; 2978; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 8 x 9.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Ghost Ranch, water in foreground and Pedernal in distance, undated; 2014.3.279; 2977; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 10 x 7.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Ghost Ranch, water in foreground and Pedernal in distance, undated; 2014.3.280; 2976; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.75 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Ghost Ranch cliffs, man in foreground, undated; 2014.3.281; 2975; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.75 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Ghost Ranch house exterior and patio, undated; 2014.3.282; 2974; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Ghost Ranch house exterior and patio, undated; 2014.3.283; 2973; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Abiquiu house before trees grew, undated; 2014.3.284; 2972; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 7.75 x 7.875 inches (Box 4)
  - View from Abiquiu house to southeast before trees grew, undated; 2014.3.285; 2971; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 8 x 8 inches (Box 4)
  - Abiquiu house, undated; 2014.3.286; 2970; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Nuns at Ghost Ranch house, circa 1947; 2014.3.287; 2969; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 8.125 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Nuns at Ghost Ranch house, circa 1947; 2014.3.288; 2968; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5.875 x 3.5 inches (Box 4)
  - Nuns at Ghost Ranch house, circa 1947; 2014.3.289; 2967; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.5 x 5.875 inches (Box 4)
  - Road, black and white photograph, undated; 2014.3.290; 2966; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.5 x 6.25 inches (Box 4)
  - Antelope at Ghost Ranch, undated; 2014.3.291; 2965; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.5 x 6.25 inches (Box 4)
  - David Oistrakh, classical violinist, undated; 2014.3.292; 2964; Seigel, Adrian; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Budapest String Quartet, undated; 2014.3.293; 2963; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Budapest String Quartet, undated; 2014.3.294; 2962; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Copy print 8 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Witter Bynner, undated; 2014.3.295; 2961; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.5 x 3.5 inches (Box 4)
  - Witter Bynner, undated; 2014.3.296; 2960; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.5 x 3.5 inches (Box 4)
  - Double exposure of man and landscape [possibly Stieglitz at Lake George], undated; 2014.3.297; 2959; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.5 x 2.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Unidentified man in front of stop sign, undated; 2014.3.298; 2958; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 9.375 x 7.5 inches (Box 4)
  - Pedro Beltran, undated; 2014.3.299; 2957; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.75 x 7.25 inches (Box 4)
  - Todd Webb, undated; 2014.3.300; 2956; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 5 x 4.25 inches (Box 4)
    Photograph possibly taken by Georgia O'Keeffe and printed by Todd Webb.
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with John Gates, undated; 2014.3.301; 2955; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 9.5 x 7.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and Helen Woodruff, undated; 2014.3.302; 2954; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.125 x 5.375 inches (Box 4)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe and unidentified female in France, undated; 2014.3.303; 2953; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 7 x 5 inches (Box 4)
  - Man with bicycle in front of building [in France], undated; 2014.3.304; 2952; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph, 3.625 x 4.75 in 3.625 x 4.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Building exterior [in France], undated; 2014.3.305; 2951; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 3.625 x 4.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Portrait of Patricia Jennings, undated; 2014.3.306; 2950; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.75 x 3.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Washington Monument, undated; 2014.3.307; 2949; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Black and white photograph 4.5 x 2.875 inches (Box 4)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe at table with scissors, circa 1948; 2014.3.308; 2948; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Color photograph 5 x 3.5 inches (Box 4)
  - Pedernal and New Mexico landscape, undated; 2014.3.309; 2947; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Color photograph 6.125 x 8.75 inches (Box 4)
  - Abiquiu house exterior, undated; 2014.3.310; 2946; Unknown; 1 Photographic Film Color transparency 8 x 10 inches (Box 4)
  - Garden, New Mexico, undated; 2014.3.311; 2945; Unknown; 1 Photographic Film Color transparency 10 x 8 inches (Box 4)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe with camera, chow, and unidentified woman on Ghost Ranch patio, undated; 2014.3.312; 2944; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Color photograph 5 x 7 inches (Box 5)
  - Unidentified man, undated; 2014.3.313; 2943; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Color photograph 4 x 5 inches (Box 5)
  - Cross, undated; 2014.3.314; 2942; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Color photograph 4 x 5 inhes (Box 5)
  - Photograph of Train at Night in the Desert painting by Georgia O'Keeffe in frame, undated; 2014.3.315; 2941; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Diffusion transfer print 4.25 x 3.375 inches (Box 4)
  - Photograph of abstract painting by Georgia O'Keeffe in frame, undated; 2014.3.316; 2940; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Diffusion transfer print 4.25 x 3.375 inches (Box 4)
  - Photograph of Church Bell, Ward, Colorado painting by Georgia O'Keeffe in frame, undated; 2014.3.317; 2939; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints Diffusion transfer print 4.25 x 3.375 in (Box 4)
- Correspondence, 1940-1963, undated; 2; 2924; The majority of letters are addressed to Georgia O'Keeffe. Arranged alphabetically by creator.
  - Adams, Ansel, 1963; 2937 (Box 5)
  - Alsdorfs, James W., undated; 2936 (Box 5)
  - Borsig, Tet Arnold von, 1950, 1955; 2935 (Box 5)
  - Callery, Mary, undated; 2934 (Box 5)
  - Falk, Frederick William, 1962; 2933 (Box 5)
  - Gates, John M.; Steuben Glass, Inc., 1940-01-24; 2932 (Box 5)
  - Girard, Marshall, 1961-08-13; 2931 (Box 5)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art; Busch-Reisinger Museum Harvard University, 1973; 2930 (Box 5)
  - Keck, Caroline, 1946-01-08; 2929 (Box 5)
  - Mayhew, Charles; Mayhew, Anne, 1959; 2928 (Box 5)
  - Moore, Charles Wickham (Wick), 1944, undated; 2927 (Box 5)
  - Pritzlaff, Richard, undated; 2926 (Box 5)
  - Seligmann, Herbert J., 1950-05-20; 2925 (Box 5)
- Drawings, undated; 3; 2922
  - Watercolor and graphite drawing on paper, unidentified creator, undated; 2923 (Oversize 2)
- Prints, 1882, undated; 4; 2917
  - Four in Hand reprinted from a lithograph by Curier and Ives, N.Y., undated; 2918 (Oversize 2)
  - L'Illustration Horticole's Raisin Alicante, 1882; 2921 (Oversize 2)
  - Reproduction of Portrait of a Young Man in Red painting by Giovanni Bellini, undated; 2920 (Oversize 2)
  - Reproduction of Profile Portrait of a Lady painting by Pisanello, undated; 2919 (Oversize 2)
- Printed Material, 1963-1974, undated; 5; 2905
  - 291 at the Washburn Gallery, exhibition brochure, 1973; 2908 (Box 5)
  - 'Eros' magazine, publication announcement, undated; 2910 (Box 5)
  - Old Mission Church at Ranchos de Taos, N. Mex., postcard, undated; 2914 (Box 5)
  - Penitente Church near Taos, N. Mex., postcard, undated; 2911 (Box 5)
  - Seven Americans at the Washburn Gallery, exhibition brochure, 1974; 2909 (Box 5)
  - Taos Pueblo, postcard, undated; 2913 (Box 5)
  - Taos Pueblo, postcard, undated; 2912 (Box 5)
  - Washington Monument and cherry blossoms, postcard, undated; 2916 (Box 5)
  - Washington Monument and pension office, undated; 2915 (Box 5)
  - 'What a Majestic Word: In Memory of Russell Varian' by Ansel Adams, publication announcement, 1963; 2907 (Oversize 2)
- Clippings, undated; 6; 2889
  - Alexander Calder sculpture, clipping, undated; 2904 (Oversize 2)
  - Article about Congress with image of the Capitol dome, clipping, undated; 2899 (Oversize 2)
  - Bust, clipping, undated; 2892 (Oversize 2)
  - The Checkered Dress by Hilda Belcher, clipping, undated; 2893 (Oversize 2)
  - Conductor, clipping, undated; 2891 (Oversize 2)
  - Gerald Heard, clipping, undated; 2890 (Oversize 2)
  - Goat, clipping, undated; 2896 (Oversize 2)
  - Horse, clipping, undated; 2895 (Oversize 2)
  - The Great Need - An Informed Opinion article with image of the Capitol dome, clipping, undated; 2898 (Oversize 2)
  - Light Work, clipping, undated; 2897 (Oversize 2)
  - Man amongst doves, clipping, undated; 2894 (Oversize 2)
  - Models in cityscape, clipping, undated; 2903 (Oversize 2)
  - Washington Monument and Lincoln Memorial, clipping, undated; 2902 (Oversize 2)
  - Washington Monument and the dome of the Capitol, clipping, undated; 2901 (Oversize 2)
  - Washington Monument seen from Lincoln Memorial, clipping, undated; 2900 (Oversize 2)